

OMAR **KASHLAN**

COMPUTER ENG & WEB DEV

CONTACT

Syria - Damascus

+963 998 136 917

OmarKashlanBusiness@hotmail.com

FOLLOW ME

facebook/omar.kashlan.5

twitter/omar kashlan

instagram/omar.kashlan

Linkedin/Omar Kashlan

LANGUAGE

ARABIC

ENGLISH

FRENCH

CERTIFICATES

HTML UX/UI

CSS C#

ICDL MICROSOFT 365

MORE ON:

https://bit.ly/3NzGQQN



ABOUT ME

Hi there, I'm Omar Kashlan.

I have a lot of experience in the field of data entry, web development (front end), video design and editing, and many other experiences related to computers and remote work.

I graduated with very high grades, ranking second in my university, and I look forward to gaining more experience and knowledge.

I am committed to delivering high-quality work and exceeding expectations, and I am excited about the opportunity to bring my skills and experience to a new role.

In general, I am very looking forward to be distinguished in what I do and I will be at the best level I can present.



EDUCATION

> UNIVERSITY OF THE PEOPLE

NOV 2021- Till Now

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science (4 Years)

> DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY

NOV 2021 - AUG 2023

Associate Degree in Computer engineering (2 Years), with ranking second in my university

> ALSAADE SCHOOL

AUG 2020 - SEP 2021

I have been awarded the Certificate of General Secondary Education -Scientific Section — having scored a general average (76.52%).



EXPERIENCE

> WEB DESIGNING

APRIL 2023 - JUNE 2023

Personal Website, check it on: https://omarkashlan.000webhostapp.com/

> DATA ENTRY CLERK

MAY 2019 - Till Now

Entering students' personal information and entering it into the local company system through Office programs such as Word and Excel programs.

> LEADER AND MANAGER ON A PROJECT

JAN 2023 - JUNE 2023

> GRAPHIC DESIGNER

OCT 2021 - JUNE 2023

Designing some vector images, illustrations, and a logo for the university's advertisements or for its website.



SKILLS

ILLUSTRATOR	• • • • •	TEAMWORK	• • • • •
HTML	• • • •	PROBLEM-SOLVING	• • • • •
CSS	• • • • •	LEADERSHIP	• • • • •
JAVA SCRPT	• • • • •	COMPUTER SKILLS	• • • • •
MS EXCEL	• • • •	GOOGLE DRIVE	••••
VIDEO EDITING	••••	WORD PROCESSING	• • • • •
SPREADSHEETS	••••	MULTI-TASKING	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
TYPING SPEED	• • • •	TIME MANAGEMENT	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$